出来吧
跟着我也挺久了说吧
有什么事
这是什么
玫瑰花礼物
还有情书
学姐我喜欢你很久了
可以做我女朋友吗
字儿写的还不错
可是我没有谈恋爱的想法
回去吧
看来你是有备而来呀
背地里打听过我吗
我的确没有男朋友
可这也不代表我就想和你谈恋爱呀
啊喜欢我很久啊
那你就继续喜欢着吧
和我有什么关系啊
还说喜欢我
喜欢我还买这种庸俗的花
你难道不知道我不喜欢这个吗
算了不用了
你不知道我喜欢什么
买回来也没有用
别再来烦我
我就谢天谢地了
哎我说你一个男生怎么被拒绝就要哭呀
爱我爱我
你怎么还会送我
不喜欢的话
看来你的爱也只是嘴上说说
哎你烦死了
你要哭死
一边哭去
别当着我的面哭
你个大男人
你哭得眼睛红红的
你不知道会想让我
算了
想知道好
那我告诉你
那大概就是看到一只可爱的小兔子
眼睛红红的娇
娇弱弱的身体还在微微发抖
你就很想啊掐住他的脖子
看他呼吸不上来
不断的用腿蹬着你
害怕了害怕就走吧
别再来了
想留下来
你想清楚了吗
行
既然你想留下来
那就要接受我有些奇怪的小癖好
我给你一个晚上的时间
过了
今晚能不能再留下来
就要看你的本事了
随便坐吧
这是我自己租的房子
用周末来住两天
那我们现在就开始吧
放松我又不会吃了你
你之前有过女朋友吗
有那你是不是
i won't stop until you
say
yes
say yes
say
yes
so i say
say
yes
i won't stop into you
say
yes
so i say it ho
i won't stop until you say you say you say you
just to say you say you say it fa
i won't back to you
say you
say you say to
say you say you now
do you mind
if i stay the night
heavy appetite
give you all the things that you lie
i know what you li
just so i can set the moon
right
gave me me me
when the sky fused in the moon
if you want it
baby
right now is the perfect time that prop
if you
won't it baby right now is the perfect of the ground
it up
deep dance with you
round a bit emery
know you love me
what you see
see you rock you to the bee of the face
should break when you
don't feel feeling mire
再也要
in spite yy
i won't stop until you
say
yes
so i say
say
yes
i won't stop into you
say you say
yes
so i say
i won't stop until you say you say
yes
say
so i say
yes
say baby
i wont stop until you say you say you say
so say you say you say you love
i want you to test this answer
insane and leave picking this tire
margot me
so impatient
as if
we can't find the light walk baby
let's get lost uh
i know you were telling me till
i met the nicodance side
billy jean anticipation in the air
started killing me
so we made it to the stage
and the macy when he had his conversation escalated to the b
when we started go
and i said i'm coming
i'll be there
so i drew my legs up the other
gion plenty hair room
and i told them slow
it down
baby be my cap for
and they'll be worry about the labs
if we get too
loud is yours
just only you know you wanna go stupid
go crazy
but not too
well
ain't heavy your babies
i won't stop until you
say
yes
say yes
so i say
yes
say yes
say it
i won't stop into you
say
yes
so i say it ho
i won't stop until you say you
say you
so to say you say baby
oh why how much
save save save save save save sa